Double Teamed! is a tv movie, drama, family film directed by Duwayne Dunham.
Heather and Heidi play volleyball for their school team, when their family decides that they need
to go to a bigger school so that they will have a better chance for scholarships.
But at the new school, the twins are discovered by the basketball coach.
Inspired by the true story of Heather and Heidi Burge.
Heather Burge, played by Poppi Monroe.
Heidi Burge, played by Annie McElwain.
Nicky Williams, played by Teal Redmann.
Larry Burge, played by Nick Searcy.
Madison Stricklin, played by Tanya Shanti Goott.
Wendall Yoshida, played by Joey Miyashima.
Double Teamed is a 2002 American biographical sports drama film released as a Disney Channel Original Movie and
based on the life stories of identical twin professional basketball players Heather and Heidi Burge.
The film premiered on January 18, 2002.
The tone is emotional.